<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Get (git) Ready on Hugo web framework for Fortinet Demos</title>
    <link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/01gettingstarted.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Get (git) Ready on Hugo web framework for Fortinet Demos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/01gettingstarted/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Task 1 - Create Github Token</title>
      <link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/01gettingstarted/2_task1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/01gettingstarted/2_task1.html</guid>
      <description>This procedure will take you through the process of creating a Github Token. This token will authenticate you to github.com. This is required in order to push or pull information from a tools server to github.com.
From your github.com home page, click the drop down next to your profile picture on the top right of the screen and select Settings On the left side of the settings screen, scroll all the way to the bottom of the list of options and select &amp;ldquo;&amp;lt;&amp;gt;Developer settings&amp;rdquo; from the menu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task 2 - Fork the Repo</title>
      <link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/01gettingstarted/3_task2.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/01gettingstarted/3_task2.html</guid>
      <description>In this task, you will fork an application repository from my github.com account into your own.
In your favorite browser, paste the below link into the URL bar. https://github.com/fortidg/FortiDevSecJuice.git At the top of the window, click on Fork. On the following page, select &amp;ldquo;Create fork&amp;rdquo; </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task 3 - Clone the Repo in Google cloud shell</title>
      <link>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/01gettingstarted/4_task3.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fortinetcloudcse.github.io/UserRepo/01gettingstarted/4_task3.html</guid>
      <description>Now that you have your own copy of the repo, you can modify it as you see fit. For this Lab, we are going to Clone the repo into the Google Cloud Shell.
From your newly forked repository on Github.com, select the &amp;ldquo;&amp;lt;&amp;gt; Code&amp;rdquo; dropdown. Click on the copy button to copy the HTTPS path to this repo. Activate the GCP Cloud Shell by clicking on the cursor icon at the top right side of the Console screen.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>